{
    "subject": "Maria_Nagaya",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Ivan_IV_of_Russia",
    "human_readable": "Maria Nagaya is married to Ivan IV of Russia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9652177691459656,
            "question": "Were there any important events during the marriage of Maria Nagaya and Ivan IV of Russia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9439979195594788,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Maria Nagaya and Ivan IV of Russia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9176459312438965,
            "question": "Who was Ivan IV of Russia married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9012733697891235,
            "question": "To which Russian ruler was Maria Nagaya married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8507670164108276,
            "question": "Who is Maria Nagaya married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8036311268806458,
            "question": "What is the name of Ivan IV of Russia's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6942809224128723,
            "question": "What can you tell about the lives of Maria Nagaya and Ivan IV of Russia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3851894736289978,
            "question": "Is Maria Nagaya known for her historical role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31635040044784546,
            "question": "Was Ivan IV of Russia a famous ruler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.271383672952652,
            "question": "What era did Ivan IV of Russia rule?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maria Nagaya is married to Ivan IV of Russia.",
            "html": "yago_24680_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Ivan IV of Russia a famous ruler?",
            "html": "yago_24680_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Maria Nagaya known for her historical role?",
            "html": "yago_24680_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell about the lives of Maria Nagaya and Ivan IV of Russia?",
            "html": "yago_24680_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_24680_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Maria Feodorovna Nagaya was the eighth wife of Ivan the Terrible, also known as Ivan IV of Russia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}